Woman's Building
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Women's Graphic Center, circa 1976-1989, Series 4:; (Box 20-23, 32-50; 5.6 linear feet)
  - Administrative Files, circa 1979-1988, 4.1:
    - Budget, Planning, 1983-1986 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Budget, Vendor Listing, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Budget, Year End Statements, 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Consignment Agreements, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Director's Report, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Educational Programs, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Educational Programs, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Estimating Jobs, circa 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Forms, circa 1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Goals and Objectives, 1979, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Graphic Center Notebook, circa 1979 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Holiday Sale, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Holiday Sale - Consignment Agreements, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Holiday Sale, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Jobs, circa 1987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - KUSC FM, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Letterpress, circa 1985 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - "Life in LA," 1983 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Marketing Study, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Memos, circa 1987 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Naiad Press, circa 1987 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) Artist in Residence Book Grant, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) Artist in Residence Book Grant, Artist Biographies, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) Artist in Residence Book Grant, Proposals, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) Artist in Residence Book Grant, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Organizational Information, circa 1979 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Postcard Project, Artists Biographies, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Proofreading, circa 1987 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Publication Project Applications, 1981-1982, (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 28-29)
    - Publicity, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Photographs, circa 1987 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Type Samples, circa 1987, (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 32-33)
    - Typesetting, circa 1987 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Work Rates, circa 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Work Schedules, 1987, March-August (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Work Schedules, September 1, 1987 - January 30, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Workshop Survey for "Feeling to Form," 1979 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Workshop Survey for "Imprint/Reprint," 1979 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Artist's Print Projects, circa 1976-1989, 4.2:
    - Alexander, Mary Barbara, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Baker, Marion A., circa 1976-1989 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Barkus, Mariona, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Beckman, Laurel, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Clark, Kathryn, circa 1980 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Chen, Carol, circa 1984-1987 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Costello, Debbie, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Gaulke, Cheri, circa 1976-1988 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Hassenger, Maren, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Identified Artists, A-B, circa 1976-1990 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Identified Artists, C-D, circa 1976-1990 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Identified Artists, E-H, circa 1976-1990 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Identified Artists, I-L, circa 1976-1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Identified Artists, M, circa 1976-1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Identified Artists, N-S, circa 1976-1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Identified Artists, T-Z, circa 1976-1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Karras, Maria, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - King, Susan, circa 1977-1985 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - King, Susan, 1978-1983 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Lawrence, Deborah F., circa 1984 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Licher, Bruce, 1979-1983 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Linn-Hughes, Mary, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - LOLA, circa 1982 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Lovin-Basch, CaroleAnn, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Maberry, Sue, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Morris, Ann, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Moore, Anne Corbett, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Muns, Marjorie, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Nishio, Linda, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Norlen, Linda, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Norman, Bonnie Thompson, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Norman, Bonnie Thompson, circa 1988 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Norman, Bonnie Thompson, 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Parson, Mary Alice, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - "The Postcard Project: Celebrating Our Heroines," 1985-1988 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Roberts, Michele, circa 1976-1987 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Rodriquez, Aleida, 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - SMarts, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Stewart, Cynthia, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Strehl, Dan, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - "Target L.A.: The Art of Survival," 1982 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Thurmond, Jane, 1981-1984 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Traction Gallery, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Unidentified Artists, circa 1980 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Wheeler, Jane, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Wolken, Ann Alexander, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Alm, Helen - Revealed To Me, circa 1974 (Box 32 (sol))
    - Bubar, Janet - Color Me Healthy, 1974 (Box 32 (sol))
    - Norman, Bonnie Thompson - Look Ahead, Los Angeles, 1989 (Box 32 (sol))
    - Identified Artists, circa 1976-1990 (Box 32 (sol))
    - Identified Artists, A-B, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 33)
    - Identified Artists, C-D, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 34)
    - Identified Artists, F-L, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 35)
    - Identified Artists, M, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 36)
    - Identified Artists, N-R, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 37)
    - Identified Artists, S-Z, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 38)
    - Identified Artists, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 39-42)
  - General Projects, circa 1976-1989, 4.3:
    - 1984: Big Brother is Watching, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Books, The Always Anonymous Beast by Lauren Wright Douglas, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Books, The Black and White of It by Ann Allen Shockley, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Books, Cherished Love by Evelyn Kennedy, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Books, Daughters of a Coral Dawn by Katherine V. Forrest, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Books, Dusty's Queen of Hearts Diner by Lee Lynch, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Books, An Emergence of Green by Katherine V. Forrest, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Books, Horizon of the Heart by Shelley Smith, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Books, The Long Train by Penny Hayes, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Books, The Love of Good Women by Isabel Miller, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Books, Loving Her by Ann Allen Shockley, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Books, Magdalena by Sarah Aldridge, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Books, The Other Side of Venus by Shirley Verel,, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Books, The Pearls by Shirley Smith, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Books, Searching for Spring by Patricia A. Murphy, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Books, To the Lightening by Catherine Ennis, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Brochures, 1978-1988 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Busines Cards, circa 1976-1988, (2 folders) (Box 23, Folder 11-12)
    - Chrysalis Postcards, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Examples of Printing Projects, 1976-1990, (8 folders) (Box 23, Folder 14-21)
    - Flyers, 1976-1987, (3 folders) (Box 23, Folder 22-24)
    - Hand Set Type Specimens: Women's Graphic Center, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - KUSC Program Guides, 1986-1987, (3 folders) (Box 23, Folder 26-28)
    - One, Two, Three, Four: a Rock 'n' Roll Quarterly, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Stationary, circa 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - "Women and the Printing Arts," 1975 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - "Women and the Printing Arts," 1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Woman's Building Brochures, circa 1976-1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Woman's Building Calendars, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Woman's Building Event Announcements, circa 1976-1989, (2 folders) (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
    - Woman's Building Event Invitations, circa 1976-1989 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Examples of Printing Projects, circa 1976 (Box sol 32)
    - Examples of Printing Projects, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 43-45)
    - Woman's Building Event Announcements, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 46-47)
    - Examples of Printing Projects, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 48-50)
- Artist's Works, 1972-1990, Series 5:; (Box 24-25, 51-53; 1.7 linear feet)
  This series contains artist's works, including books, cards, postcards,
  - de Bretteville, Sheila, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Edelson, Mary Beth, 1972-1979 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Hooper, Sally, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Identified Artists, A-C, circa 1976-1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Identified Artists, D-E, circa 1976-1990 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Identified Artists, F-G, circa 1976-1990 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Identified Artists, H-K, circa 1976-1990 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Identified Artists, L, circa 1976-1990 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Identified Artists, M-N, circa 1976-1990 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Identified Artists, O-R, circa 1976-1990 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Identified Artists, S, circa 1976-1990 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Identified Artists, T-Z, circa 1976-1990 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Irene Dogmatic, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - King, Susan, 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - King, Susan, 1975, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Lacy, Suzanne, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Luizzi, Connie, circa 1976-1990 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - McGee, Micki, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Marsh, Cindy, circa 1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Mums, Majorie, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Norman, Bonnie Thompson, circa 1980-1986 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Postcard Project, 1985-1988, (2 folders) (Box 24, Folder 28-29)
  - Rachel, Vaughan, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Raven, Arlene, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - A, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - B, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - C, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - D, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - E-F, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - G, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - H, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - I-J, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - K, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - L, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - M, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - N-Q, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - R, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - S, 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 10-11)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - T-V, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Responses to "What is Feminist Art?" - W-Z, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Shoshannah, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified Artists, circa 1976-1990, (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 15-16)
  - Identified Artists, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 51)
  - Marsh, Cindy, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 52)
  - Identified Artists, circa 1976-1989 (Box OV 53)
- Grants, 1974-1992, Series 6:; (Box 25-30; 5.3 linear feet)
  This series documents both the proposed and funded grant projects undertaken by the Woman's Building. Files typically contain the grant application, related correspondence, project development, and interim and final reports. The files are arranged alphabetically by grant agency.
  - Ahmanson Foundation, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Ahmanson Foundation, 1985-1989 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Apple Grant, Alliance of Women's Art Organizations, 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 19-20)
  - ARCO Foundation, Intergenerational Artists' Book Workshop, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - The Argyros Foundation, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Armand Hammer Foundation, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Arts, Inc. Consultation, circa 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Arts, Inc. Loan Payment, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Art Matter, Inc., 1989 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Atlantic Richfield Corporation, 1982-1985 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Atlantic Richfield Corporation, 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - B. Dalton Booksellers Application, Women Writers Series, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Betty Clair McMurray Foundation, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Brody Arts Fund, 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Budget, 1988-1990 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - California Community Foundation Applications, 1985-1988 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - California/International Arts Foundation, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, "The Androgynous Hamlet: A New Alienation," 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, "Ariadne: A Social Art Network," 1978 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artistic and Administrative Development Program, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artistic and Administrative Development Program, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities Grant (Suzanne Lacy), 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities Grant (Faith Wilding), 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities Grant (Mary Elizabeth Jones and Deanne Belinoff), 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities Grant (Paula Lumbard, Judith Baca, and Varnette Honeywood), 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities Grant (Varnette Honeywood), 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities Grant (Suzanne Lacy), 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Suzanne Lacy), 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Mary-Linn Hughes), 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Cheri Gaulke), 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Anne Finger), 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Anne Finger), 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Karen Holden), 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Bonnie Thompson Norman), 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Anne Finger), 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Gloria Alvarez), 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Cheri Gaulke), 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Bonnie Thompson Norman), 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Anne Finger), 1990 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Communities (Gloria Alvarez), 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Residence (Holly Prado), 1975 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Social Institutions (Deborah Lawrence), 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Artists-in-Social Institutions (Michele Clinton), 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Development Director Grant, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Expanding Public Participation Grant, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Expanding Public Participation Grant, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, "Eyes of Art: Video Artists View Women Artists," 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Gallery Program, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Gallery Program, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Gallery Program - Grant Invoices, 1985-1987 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, "Inside/Outside: An Exhibition of 18 Bay Area Women," 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Organizational Grant, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Organizational Grant, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Organizational Grant, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Organizational Grant for Short-Term Technical Assistance Program, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Paradise Press, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Theatre Arts Grant, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Touring Program Grant for "Sabia," 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, "A Tribute to Women Artists," 1976 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Visual Arts Grant, 1988-1989 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Visual Arts Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, "West Coast Women's Art Movement: A Video Documentary," 1976 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, "The Woman's Building at the 1893 Chicago World's Columbian Exposition," 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, "Women and Money," 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Women's Graphic Center, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Women's Graphic Center, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Women's Graphic Center - Finances 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Women's Graphic Center, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, Women's Graphic Center, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Application, "Women in the Printed Arts," 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - California Arts Council (CAC) Payments, Visual Arts Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - California Council for the Humanities Application, "Violent Media Images of Women" Exhibition, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - The Candle Foundation, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Carter Hawley Hale Stories, Inc., 1985 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Catalog Grant, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Chevron Corporation, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - City Arts Project, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Affairs Grant Program, Application, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Affairs Grant Program, Application, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Affairs Grant Program, Application for "A Sense of Place" Exhibition, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Affairs Grant Program, Applications for Writing Workshop, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Affairs Grant Program, Grant Applications and Contracts, 1988-1990 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Affairs Grant Program, Grant Contract, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Affairs Grant Program, "Textiles as Texts: Art of Hmong Women from Laos," 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - City of Los Angeles Cultural Affairs Grant Program, Visual Arts Application, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - City of Los Angeles Department of Telecommunications, Grant Application for "Women's Views: Life in Los Angeles," 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
  - City of Los Angeles Municipal Arts Department Grant Application, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - City of Los Angeles Municipal Arts Department Grant Application, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Coca Cola, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Community-based Free Standing Educational Institutions, Exemplary Grants Projects, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Compliants of Employment Discrimination, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA), CETA Administration for City Arts (CAFTA) Termination, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Application, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Application, Spinning-Off, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Grant, Agency Funding Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Application, Community Access Development Project, 1979-1981 (Box 27, Folder 16-17)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Application, Community Access Development Project, Project Activity Reports, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Application, Community Media Resources Project, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Application, Community Media Resources Project, Reporting Tips, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Application - Graphics Workshop, Women's Publication House, and Video Community Outreach - Contract Modification Form, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Application - Graphics Workshop, Women's Publication House, and Video Community Outreach - Appeal for Denial of Grant, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Application - Graphics Workshop, Women's Publication House, and Video Community Outreach - Draft, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Application - Graphics Workshop, Women's Publication House, and Video Community Outreach - Summary Project Proposal, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Application - Graphics Workshop, Women's Publication House, and Video Community Outreach - Worksite Contracts, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Application - Graphics Workshop, Women's Publication House, and Video Community Outreach - Monthly Worksite Evaluation Report, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA), Spinning-Off, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Grant, United Way Operating Expense Summary, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Training Information, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Worksite Contracts, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Corporate Grant Research, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - "Cross Pollination" Grant Application, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Dayton Hudson Foundation, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Demographic Information for Grant Writing, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 35)